the last few months have been filled
with ups and downs
on the one hand we are dealing with the
anxiety of the pandemic and catching the
virus
while on the other hand the constant
variations between
lockdown and unlock and lockdown again
has taken a toll on everyone's mental
health
here are a few tips to help you deal
with the current situation
get rid of rigid beliefs like things
should be my way or everything
must go back to the way it was
these rigid beliefs these shoulds and
must lead to a lot of distressing
emotions
instead replace that with it would be
great if everything
went back to the way it was however
i accept it the way it is right now
acceptance is the key the next one is
you need a constant in your life
create a constant it can be a plant
a pet a hobby or a routine
it will give you a sense of certainty
for tomorrow
and finally think bigger than yourself
help other people help those in need
help those in crisis a lot of times it
gives you a sense of purpose
in your life these recent events have
shaken everyone
change can sometimes be painful however
it can lead to something amazing
remember with the right preparation
every challenge is just another bump on
the road
that we can learn from and move ahead
here